<Page loaded="pageLoaded" class="page" xmlns="http://www.nativescript.org/tns.xsd">

	<ActionBar title="Special Diet Recipes" class="action-bar">
	</ActionBar>
	<ScrollView>
		<StackLayout class="home-panel">
			<!--Add your page content here-->
			<Label textWrap="true" text="Welcome to
Special Diet Recipies" class="h2 description-label" />
			<Image src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/graphic-design-portfolio/image_SpecialDietRecipes.png" />
			<DockLayout width="100%" height="50" style.backgroundColor="lightgray" stretchLastChild="true" style="color:white; text-align: center;">
				<Label textWrap="true" text="HOME" dock="left" backgroundColor="red" style="padding: 10%;" />
				<Label textWrap="true" text="RECIPIES" dock="left" backgroundColor="green" style="padding: 10%;" />
				<Label textWrap="true" text="BMI CALCULATOR" dock="left" backgroundColor="blue" style="padding: 10%;" />
				<Label textWrap="true" text="FOOD FACTS" backgroundColor="orange" style="padding: 10%;" />
			</DockLayout>
			<Label textWrap="true" text="Special Diet Recipes is designed for people with diabetes, kidney and heart problems. To help you find recipes that are made
			specifically for your special diet restrictions. Recipes originate from the American Diabetes Association, Davita Dialysis,
			and the American Heart Association. And they are truly mouth watering! Tons of recipe categories; including Appetizers,
			Breakfast, Brunch, Lunch, Dinner, Snacks, Desserts, Budget Meals, Soups, Sandwiches, and much more... Application Features:
			- Complete recipe easy to follow directions, ingredients, and reviews - Full Sharing of recipes to twitter, facebook,
			pintrest, and more - Search recipes by meal type, ingredients, or food title - Cooking videos and pictures - and More...
			Here's your chance to impress your friends and family members with your ability to cook excellent mouth watering meals
			that fit their strict diet restrictions! Help make planning your next diet restricted meal easier than you could have
			even imagined possible with Special Diet Recipes!"
			 class="h2 description-label" />
			<Label textWrap="true" text="&copy; 2017 Special Diet Recipies
			
			JPPM Solutions - All Rights Reserved"
			 class="h2 footer-label" />		
			 
		</StackLayout>	
	</ScrollView>

</Page>